{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20desert%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sahara%20Desert",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Gobi%20Desert",
        "Arabian%20Desert",
        "Kalahari%20Desert"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20longest%20river%20in%20Europe%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Volga%20River",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Danube%20River",
        "Loire%20River",
        "Dnieper%20River"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20lake%20by%20surface%20area%20in%20North%20America%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Lake%20Superior",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Great%20Slave%20Lake",
        "Lake%20Michigan",
        "Great%20Bear%20Lake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20highest%20mountain%20range%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Himalayas",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rocky%20Mountains",
        "Andes",
        "Alps"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20rainforest%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon%20Rainforest",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Congo%20Rainforest",
        "Daintree%20Rainforest",
        "Tongass%20Rainforest"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20most%20active%20volcano%20in%20Europe%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mount%20Etna",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mount%20Vesuvius",
        "Stromboli",
        "Mount%20Pelee"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20tropical%20rainforest%20in%20Africa%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Congo%20Rainforest",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Madagascar%20Rainforest",
        "Ituri%20Rainforest",
        "Tongass%20Rainforest"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20longest%20river%20in%20Asia%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Yangtze%20River",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ganges%20River",
        "Mekong%20River",
        "Yellow%20River"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20desert%20in%20Australia%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Great%20Victoria%20Desert",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Simpson%20Desert",
        "Gibson%20Desert",
        "Tanami%20Desert"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20is%20the%20highest%20mountain%20in%20North%20America%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Denali%20(Mount%20McKinley)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mount%20Logan",
        "Mount%20Saint%20Elias",
        "Pico%20de%20Orizaba"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
